Hello everyone, thank you very much to all the guests for taking time out of their busy schedules to attend our Cologne 6 press conference and user exchange conference.
In fact, during the preparation stage, we were a little worried that because of the epidemic, many users may not be able to come to the scene.
But now that we have so many new friends and old friends sitting together, we are very pleased.
On the one hand, this can show that everyone is very supportive of our work.
On the other hand, I also feel that in fact, everyone also needs such a platform to interact and learn from each other.
This is already our second user exchange conference.
We hope to continue this event in a normal way.
Every year, we provide such a platform to our users,
so that everyone can interact with each other about some of the pain points and difficulties in the 3D transformation process,
or some of the excitement and surprise points in the process of use,
to help us improve our products better and then provide better services to everyone.
Today, our schedule is quite tight.
Everyone may know by looking at the schedule table.
We also hope to present more content to everyone in a limited time.
First of all, we would like to invite Jaden Oh, the founder of CLO.
He will introduce the development process of CLO to everyone through a video.
After the video is finished, he will connect with Jaden Oh in Korea.
If you have any questions about CLO, you can ask him directly.
Now, let's first learn about the development process of CLO through this video.
Hello.
I am Jaden Oh.
I am the founder of CLO Virtual Fashion.
It is a pity to talk about this video due to COVID-19,
but it is really nice to meet the Chinese users for the first time.
Today, we are going to talk about how our company has grown from a user and technology point of view.
Our company was founded in 2009.
And in the video you can see now,
this is the first version of CLO's software.
Although it was not used,
it is the first product made with the idea of targeting fashion designers.
Let's take a look.
It was a product that was reflected in real-time 3D
by using fast simulation technology to modify the pattern like this.
The color and texture were also changed.
At that time, I believed that this product would be used well in the actual work of a fashion designer.
However, most of the reactions were,
It looks fun, but I can't use it.
So, at the fashion school, it was useful for education.
So, I went to various fashion schools to introduce it.
Then, for the first time, I really needed our software,
and I met the person I had been waiting for.
It's this person.
His hobby is fun.
It's virtual cosplay.
What he does as a hobby is to dress up as a virtual character like this.
But why was he enthusiastic about our software?
Why was he enthusiastic about our software?
I looked at why.
The existing tools have to make wrinkles one by one like this in 3D.
If you want to fix something, you have to do it again from the beginning.
So only CG experts could make clothes.
And people who do this as a hobby of virtual cosplay
It was a situation where I couldn't even imagine making clothes.
For this reason, people who do virtual cosplay as a hobby
I became enthusiastic about our tool.
I looked at this market.
There are 2 million users worldwide.
It is even possible to sell clothes.
You can make about 1,000 dollars a month.
So I started adding the features that these users wanted.
To bring avatars,
I developed the OBJ Collada File Import function.
I added various functions and commercialized them.
That's how it came out.
This is the Marvellous Designer 2 that came out at the end of 2010.
If you look at the demo,
From this point on, you can see that the feeling of commercial software is a little better.
Avatars, clothes, UI, etc. are much better.
Also, virtual cosplay users can easily buy software.
I also built a website that can be sold online.
As time went by, there was a rumor.
Suddenly, I got a call from a large CG studio called Weta Digital.
Because the demand for making clothes for digital characters was the same.
Not only virtual cosplay users, but also CG companies.
I made a lot of money.
It began to be used by CG companies.
At Weta Digital,
When we made Tintin,
We started using our software for the first time.
This costume is the first costume made with our software.
After years of hard work,
Currently, almost all CG, computer graphics, and studios
We're going to make movies and animations with our software.
The same goes for Pixar.
After the movie market, our software has also begun to be used in the computer game market.
Our software is being used to make clothes in most games.
How was the fashion industry while there were more users in the film and animation game field?
Claw has also been released from the beginning with the CG software, but there were no real users.
It was just a trial of a few companies and a few pattern CAD companies.
However, we received functional requests from these users and continued to develop.
The first target was a fashion designer.
Because we knew that the functionality and usability were insufficient, we added the DXF compatibility function to make pattern companies use it.
We also added the avatar sizing function, which was the biggest demand at the time.
However, there were still no users.
Because there were no users, it was difficult to figure out what the real problem was.
So we decided.
We went directly to the actual company and verified it with our software.
It was POC.
At that time, I was interested in diesel, steph, adidas, louis vuitton, etc.
I analyzed the requirements of the POC and continued to develop.
In the beginning, we developed a lot of functions to improve usability, such as DAW.
The representative is this internal component cross-interference allowance.
It's hard to believe, but in the past, the necessary internal component cross-interference was not allowed to make padding, so we had to split the components one by one.
It must have been really hard.
There was also a time when there was no 3D undo read function.
We developed various functions to improve usability, including one-to-n sewing.
Freeze, strengthen, press, tag, m-to-n, sewing, etc.
Meanwhile, we are developing must-have features that fashion users really need.
Stitch, button, piping, measure function.
Sim tape, colorway.
Fabric kit, puckering, rendering, etc.
All of these are necessary functions.
Also, as pattern companies started to make patterns in CLO, not CAD, they began to develop various CAD functions for pattern companies in earnest.
These are the functions.
And recently, fashion designers have also started to design using CLO.
I started to install various functions for designers.
In addition, by installing high-end rendering functions,
users began to create works like real life.
After four years of effort, users began to increase in earnest since 2017.
This year, the number of real-life users has increased by nearly three times last year.
Currently, many fashion companies are innovating the process using CLO.
Digital fashion innovation, which started from the field of virtual cosplay, has moved on to the field of movies, games, and fashion.
Then, what will happen in the future?
All users in the field of movies, games, and fashion were experts.
We are now trying to create software that can be designed by ordinary people, that is, people who do not know patterns, and your family.
With this goal in mind, we have recently developed various automation functions.
Auto-grading allows you to adjust the pattern size according to the avatar size with a single mouse click without pattern knowledge.
Auto-Sewing is in version 6.0, and if you just place the pattern like this video, it will be automatically sewed.
It automatically makes it possible to adjust the size and pose without the help of other people.
This video is the result.
Now it's the last one.
As in the next video, it will be possible to modify the style line right away in 3D.
Thank you for listening to it for a long time.
Thank you for watching.
Now let's start the long-term connection, Jaden.
If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us.
Thank you.
You can try to contact me.
Yes, please.
Jaden, are you with me?
You can see me on the screen.
Before we ask you questions, I'll ask a question.
One of our viewers is also a fan of Jaden.
She is studying in Germany right now.
She had a question for us in advance.
Her question is from a simulation point of view.
Why does the same thing happen to us?
Let's ask Jayden how he answered this question.
Jayden, I have a question for you.
From the perspective of simulation,
can you answer why the shape changes a little bit
when you do multiple simulations of the same object?
Yes.
Simulation algorithms are being processed using multiple CPUs.
There is a randomness in the collision detection of
avatars and other objects.
Randomness occurs.
But the fabric is the same.
There is a randomness in collision detection,
so there is a little bit of a difference
when you do a similar simulation every time.
But the result is the same.
Jayden's answer is that our simulation
is based on multiple CPUs.
So in the simulation process,
there are some differences between avatars and clothing,
and there are some conflicts between the two fabrics.
When the conflict is processed,
there may be some differences in the simulation every time.
But the characteristics of the fabric itself
are consistently simulated.
Another small reason is that
sometimes we wear clothes,
and it is impossible for the shape to remain the same
every time you wear clothes.
It is also the same principle.
Do you have any more questions?
Hello, my question is,
when we wear clothes,
because there are many layers of clothing,
but when we make clothes,
we can't determine which layer is where.
So when we wear clothes,
we have to drag each layer.
When you control 6.0,
do you have any functions
to solve the pain of our users?
There is no way to drag, right?
That is to say,
when we wear clothes,
there are many layers.
But when we make clothes,
we can't determine which layer is where,
which layer is on the second layer.
When we make clothes,
we have to drag each layer.
Just like when we use AI,
it can divide the layers.
The first layer is the front and the back.
The second layer is the pocket.
The third layer is the back pocket.
You want to define the layer.
Yes.
Okay, let me ask.
Jayden,
when you make clothes,
do you have any functions
to define the layer?
For example,
in the case of AI,
you can define the layer like this.
But in Clue,
when you make several layers of clothes,
can you define the layer?
What do you think about this part?
There is already a layer function,
but there is already a function
to define the layer
when you wear several layers.
In fact,
there is already a function
to define the layer in our software.
I don't know if you know about it.
There is a function to define the layer.
The layer inside and the layer outside
can be defined.
Yes, there are only two layers.
I can only put one layer in the front,
one layer in the back,
and one layer in the front.
There is no way to define the first layer.
The first layer is the front,
and the second layer is the back.
Or the pocket is the second layer.
You can define the layer here.
For example,
I want to define the pocket
as the top of the first layer
and the front layer as the second layer.
That's what I want to do.
Yes, yes.
Recently,
the 5.2 version
and the layer simulation
have been changed.
The way they changed
is the way the user
wants to use it.
That's how they changed it.
So,
if you put the pocket
on the first layer
and the other layer on the second layer,
the pocket will go inside
and the layer on the top will come out.
That's how the layer simulation
has been changed.
Yes.
From the 5.2 version,
it has already changed
in this direction.
For example,
you can define
if the pocket is on the first layer,
it will be on the outer layer,
and the second layer on the back
will be on the inner layer.
It can be defined like this
and it will be lined up like this.
Yes, yes.
You can ask the teacher
in detail
during the break.
Thank you.
Are there any other questions?
This way.
I heard that
6.0 will add
the riding function.
The introduction just now
was very brief.
Let's see if this function
can be introduced by
Jordan.
Actually,
I will answer you
about this part first.
Later,
we will introduce
the introduction of
the 6.0 new function
in an hour.
There will be a detailed introduction
in that.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you.
Jordan,
I heard that
you want to see
the riding function
that can be used
to view
grades
and values
in the program.
So,
you can ask the teacher
in detail
during the break.
Yes, yes.
Are there any other questions?
This is a rare opportunity.
Come on.
Give me the microphone.
So,
when the CLE version
of CLE is introduced,
does it have
some specific
file format?
Yes,
it does.
So,
can this format
be a little wider?
It's not just
BXF.
BXF?
Yes,
this is the format.
Because there are many
kinds of software.
For example,
if I switch to
another version
or something,
will it be
a little wider?
In this way,
there may be
more people
who use it.
For example,
what format
do you want to introduce?
For example,
the AMA of
DXF.
Yes, yes.
The AMA of
TIP,
TPP.
Because it's
very difficult to
introduce a software.
The AMA of
DXF?
Yes, yes.
Okay,
let me ask.
This person
is asking,
we only have
AMA and
ASTM
in the DXF format
that we are
promoting.
Is there any other
possibility of
supporting other
formats?
What is
TIP
behind DXF?
TIP,
for example,
is there
any other
possibility of
supporting other
formats?
Yes,
well,
it can be
used,
but
well,
yes,
it can be
used.
He's
holding
us
back.
He may
not know
this format very
well.
That is,
if it is
really necessary,
it can be
developed,
but we
may need to
understand
it.
I think
we can
do this.
Okay,
but
which
CAD
will we
use
only
the
format
we
can only
use
in this format?
Tori?
Tori.
Is it
Japanese?
Tori,
the Japan
CAD
Tori format
that
comes
out
I have a question, I am very curious about the difference between ModsDesign and Claw,
or maybe your kind of plan about these two software, so as you said at the beginning,
so your user is more from CG area, more from costume designer,
so are they going to be using ModsDesign rather than Claw,
or will Claw be more fashion industry focus, so probably going to be connect with production more,
so how is your plan?
Do you want to say it in Chinese again?
Would you repeat your question more clearly?
It's just I am curious about your plan between ModsDesign and Claw,
so will Claw be really fashion industry focus software rather than ModsDesign,
and I make myself clean?
I think Claw is more for fashion, but I don't know if that's the right way to explain it?
What's the difference between the two?
Yes, I think you are right.
The main difference between ModsDesign and Claw is that
ModsDesign is more focused on content graphics,
and Claw is more for fashion,
but I think in terms of functions,
since a few years ago,
we started to separate a few functions for both software,
so now MD has its own specific functions for CG industries,
and Claw also has its own functions,
but I think in the future,
I think Claw, we will do in this direction,
but I don't know,
I don't understand what is your intention about this question.
If you want, you want to have more functions,
or CG functions,
in Claw,
then I think it is possible,
we can add MDCFG functions into Claw.
It is possible.
Okay, thank you.
Let me give you an answer from Jayden.
As Claw said,
the difference between ModsDesign and Claw is that
ModsDesign is more focused on the processing of CG games,
and Claw is more focused on the fashion industry.
In terms of functions,
just like what he said in the previous video,
the functions may be very similar in the early stages,
but as time goes by,
the difference between these two products is getting bigger and bigger.
In ModsDesign,
there are more special functions needed in CG,
and then Claw will add some functions needed by more clothing companies,
so the difference between the two products in the future will be bigger and bigger.
Thank you.
Okay, thank you.
I have two questions.
The first question is that
more and more customers are using virtual models to do some movements,
because a lot of fabric materials
are not performing well under normal conditions.
So we will, for example,
do some movement-like movements,
or some walking-like movements.
But when we are adjusting the model,
there are a few problems.
The first one is the location of the bones in the details of the hand,
such as the hand,
the feet,
as well as the head.
Some of these adjustments are not easy to operate,
especially the hand,
which is often twisted,
and then the feet,
which is also a big problem.
So I wonder if this has been improved in the future.
The second question is that
more and more designers can use Claw to make some changes,
and there is also a board designer who can work directly on the board.
So we would like to ask the next question.
In the 2D version software,
is there a plan to directly implement this board function
like ET?
Okay, let me ask.
Jayden,
Laura from Cashin asked this question.
There are two questions.
The first one is that
when you do avatar sizing,
especially the fingers,
the ankles,
and the head,
you can use this part often.
It's hard to do.
There is this part.
So is there a plan to improve this part in the future?
This is the first question.
The second question is...
What was the second question again?
Oh, it's this.
The CAD function.
We have added a lot of functions
that can be modified in the 2D version.
Is there a plan like this in the future?
Can we make a pattern right away
without the CAD function in Clue?
Is there a plan like this?
I'm asking these two questions.
Okay.
The answer to the second question is
to go in that direction.
Without the CAD function,
we can make a pattern in Clue
so that we can make a pattern in Clue.
For example,
we can make a pattern in Clue
without the CAD function,
so that we can make a pattern in Clue.
So that we can make a pattern in Clue.
Actually, a lot of people
are using the pattern in Clue
a lot of people are using the pattern in Clue.
So the CAD function can be modified.
So we can make a pattern in Clue.
He answered the second question first.
That is, we are now
going in this direction,
which is to make a pattern in Clue directly.
In fact, we also have a lot of users
who have already done this.
Make a pattern in Clue directly.
And then we have some related
pattern functions,
which we are also constantly
adding to Clue.
And the first question is...
Q. What are the mistakes
we make in our fingers
and the rest of our hair?
Q. What are the mistakes we make in our fingers
For example, when changing
the size of fingers,
we sometimes make the mistake
to make the fingers in a shape
that we don't want.
We make some mistakes
Can I change the pose?
When I change the avatar's size and pose?
Not the size, but when you pose.
I have a question.
I don't know which side is more comfortable.
You can ask the teacher directly.
If you can solve it, you can calculate it.
I don't know which side is more comfortable.
Then you can ask the teacher directly.
If you think it's inconvenient to ask,
we'll let him know.
Thank you.
You have more questions?
Do you want to ask?
I have one question.
Currently, in the past three years,
we've used the fabric kit manually,
which is really tricky for us to keep the consistency
handling by different handlers.
Is it possible that in the future,
you'll develop the fabric analyzer in an automatic way
as other brands so that we can make sure
marrying the physical fabric can be easier?
And it can be controlled in a better way?
Yes.
Do you have any plans to make automatic fabric measuring equipment?
Of course, we plan to study and develop the most basic things,
so that users can easily test and measure the fabric.
This study is still ongoing.
But I think next year,
we can show the next version of the fabric kit.
With this fabric kit,
once the manual works,
it should be removed in the next year.
Okay.
And another question is that
the more we proceed with 3D,
the more we regret is that
when we build the 3D sample,
it's better to handle by the tech part,
the technical people.
But the designers also want to do the design by themselves,
but they prefer to just change,
apply the different colors or trims or prints on the 3D sample.
So is there any software in the future
so that the designer can just switch the colorway
and the design side
without touching the sample?
Can we develop a special software for designers?
For designers,
do you have any plans to develop a software
that only changes the texture and color?
Just color and texture?
Yes.
For designers,
we only change the color and trims.
We don't change the pattern.
We don't change the silhouettes or anything like that?
Yes.
For 3D clothes,
for example,
if all the pattern makers make it,
then we give it to the designer,
and the designer only changes the texture, trim, and color.
Yes, yes.
We don't have any plans for the software,
but in the cloth set,
we only change the material color.
We only change the configurator.
And also some trims.
Yes, trims.
Can you change the trims in the cloth set?
Trim?
Yes, trims.
Like buttons, zippers, things like that?
Yes.
We have plans to do that,
but the material configurator is the first,
and then the trims.
Yes, yes.
The second question,
we haven't decided to have a software for designers.
But we're planning to put the functions you mentioned
on the cloth set platform,
and that platform will have this function.
We can change the fabric,
and the color,
and then add all the things you mentioned.
And another question about cloth set.
Because in China,
currently cloth sets,
that still runs really slow, which will cause the efficiency problem for us, and communication
as well as data work.
So is there any solution for that part?
Yes, we have a solution for that part.
Jade, our crosshair is too slow in China.
So do you have any plans to fix it?
We are working hard on it, and we are still working on it.
I will tell you about the plans later.
We are still working on it.
Yes, because we understand the situation now.
We have already set the priority to the highest level.
Thank you.
I am very curious.
Jade, as the founder, what do you think is the biggest strength of CLO compared to other 3D software on the market?
Jade, as the founder, what are the strengths of CLO compared to other competitive software?
What is our strength?
Oh, sorry.
Compared to other 3D software, there are several 3D software,
but my biggest strength is that we can design directly.
We can design the same design, but at a different time,
and we can design a variety of outfits.
I think this is the biggest difference.
Yes.
So he said,
he thinks the biggest difference is that our software can be designed in a very intuitive way,
and in the shortest time, we can create a variety of outfits.
This is one of our advantages.
And in addition,
I didn't talk about the Genie project just now,
but in the future,
there will be a lot of people who don't know about fashion,
and experts,
and people who don't know about patterns,
and we will be able to design those tools,
and those tools will be included in CLO.
Yes.
Just like what Jade said in the video,
our development direction is to make it easy for ordinary people to use our software to develop.
Although our software is already the most convenient to use in all of our products,
we still need to make it even more convenient.
So this is our main development direction in the future.
This is also one of our biggest advantages.
I would like to ask,
when we scan the fabric,
some of the fabric has a private line,
but when you put it in your environment,
it usually shows the whole piece of fabric,
whether it is metal or silk.
But is there a step,
for example,
when I put a private line or a small piece of fabric together,
the fabric turns into silk?
I think the technical staff can answer this question.
There is a new feature.
In the 6.0 new feature,
there is also an introduction.
You can listen to the introduction later.
If you have any questions,
please feel free to ask them in the Q&A section.
Thank you.
In the back.
I know that coke is mainly for clothing.
I am a teacher in a
I want to ask,
We can do some work in the shopping mall, especially the models.
Because I know that we don't have a fixed model, so it's more difficult to form.
Which company are you from?
I'm from Canon.
Oh, okay.
Jayden, this person is from a bag company.
So in the case of clothes, it's easy to wear because there are avatars.
But in the case of bags, there are no specific avatars.
So do you have a solution for this?
I'm not sure if this is satisfactory, but I know that there are bags that are provided with cubes and avatars.
Yes, that's right.
There is also a badge point.
Should I try that too?
Yes.
Because I just asked you which company you are from.
Because if it is through our training, we should know that we have some internal sachets, some square bodies to make bags.
You think these are not enough, right?
So what kind of model do you want to have?
What does it need?
Because it is a secondary bag.
Because we don't usually see those bags.
It's actually a handbag.
The shape of the bag is very different.
It's not like the square bag we think of.
The square bag is too ordinary.
We've seen a lot of them.
Do you have any special tools to replace this model to make it form quickly?
You mean you want to have all kinds of shapes?
Yes.
Make it form quickly.
I don't need to process it.
I just keep pulling it.
We've done the training.
The training has been completed.
But we still feel that it needs to be more...
Because the bag is made of plastic.
It's just hanging on the bag.
But the handbag is different.
It needs to be frozen.
And then it's hardened.
And then it's frozen again.
And then it's hardened again.
We have to do some defensive work.
So that the bag can be formed.
I think it's possible.
Okay.
I'll talk to him.
Jayden.
He knows that we have the cube.
But I think that's not enough.
I want it to be in a variety of shapes.
Like the costume.
If you just put the avatar in,
I want the silhouette to come out right away.
I want it to be easier.
Yes.
So...
There's a page point in the asset we've put in this time.
There was no page point in the past.
So I think we can use it.
We've got a variety of objects.
It's a very good idea because we've been developing it.
It's not like that.
Yes.
Then, like you said.
If there's a shape.
If there's a shape,
You can make it.
Just like you just said.
Maybe the shape of each bag.
Yes.
If there's a shape,
Maybe there's a shape.
Yes.
If there's a shape,
It's possible.
You can make it.
Yes.
If there's a shape,
I can make it.
so that we can communicate with you in more detail
and see what shapes you need
so that we can put them in the development later on.
Is that okay? Thank you.
This way.
Hi, I'd like to ask, in the new function of Chrome 6.0,
is there any improvement in the fitting effect?
Or how many percent can the similar parts of the fittings reach so far?
Thank you.
Okay, thank you.
The content of this question is
whether there is an improvement in the accuracy of the fittings in the U.S. version.
And how many percent of accuracy do we have in terms of fittings?
How much?
How accurate are the fittings?
In terms of fittings?
Yes, in terms of fittings.
Fitting?
Yes.
Well, actually, fittings are
the accuracy of the fittings
due to the influence of the fabric moisture measurement.
If that's accurate,
then the simulation will be accurate, too.
This is a very vague question,
but when we actually did the fittings and did the fabric research,
we were very satisfied with the result.
Oh, okay.
That's all I can say now.
In fact, yesterday, the PLOS fitting service was released in Britain.
Yes.
It was released, so we can do more experiments through it.
I think we can do more experiments through the beta version.
Yes.
Yes, I think we can do more experiments through the beta version.
Yes, thank you.
As Jayden just said,
in terms of fittings,
the accuracy of the fabric moisture measurement is the most influential.
So, first of all, we have to see how accurate the fabric measurement is.
In addition, we have actually done some survey research among our users.
We want to see if everyone is satisfied with the accuracy of the fitting.
Basically, the answer we get is that they are satisfied.
They can reach the current state of their needs.
A while ago, we just released the fitting test version of our CLOSET.
We have a test version of the fitting.
There will be some simple introductions in the future.
The accumulation of these data will also make the fitting results more accurate.
Thank you.
Do you have any more questions?
I heard in the Q&A just now that our families can use this feature.
Yes.
I wonder if this could be used for drawing on one's body.
Like a fashion drawing.
The result would look like a paper.
Do you have any ideas for this?
Hmm.
Jayden, when you were talking about PPTs,
We are trying to make clothes for the general public and our family.
So what this person is thinking is that if you just draw a line in the avatar, the clothes will come out right away.
Is this the direction?
I don't know if it's enough to draw a line, but it looks like that.
We are trying to change the silhouette, length, style, and shape of the avatar in 3D.
And we are trying to make the pattern to come out accurately.
Maybe it's not necessarily like you said, drawing from the human body.
Maybe it's about making money.
Maybe it's about the model.
Or maybe it's based on the existing 3D clothes.
For example, like what was explained in the video earlier,
changing these style lines to make it easier and quicker to change the form of the model.
Maybe it's also in that direction.
In short, we are continuously developing in this direction.
Hello, can you talk a little bit about the wearing difference?
Sometimes, the clothes are packed tightly.
I think there is no case where you need to turn it off when you want to open it, and you don't need to turn it off when you want to close it.
No matter how you turn it, it won't penetrate.
Oh, no matter how you turn it, it won't penetrate.
Okay, I'll ask him.
This person is asking, when we're doing a costume simulation, if we pull it a little bit, if we pull it with a little bit of force, for example, the costume inside can come out, right?
There's something like this.
So, if you set it up, no matter how hard you pull it, it won't come out.
Can you do something like this?
Yes, that's the layer function I explained earlier.
If you set up a layer,
it will help in a situation like that.
But the layer function can't always be the answer.
If you set up a layer in a specific situation, there will be a situation where there is no conflict, so you have to use it according to the situation.
In a situation like this, it's good to set up a layer function.
So, the question you just asked,
if you use the layer function we introduced earlier,
it should be able to solve this problem to a certain extent.
But the layer function doesn't mean that it can 100% solve all these penetrating problems.
It may also have to be analyzed in detail according to different situations.
So, if you have a problem that is easy to penetrate, you can ask our technical group teacher.
I'm sorry, I'm not sure what you're talking about.
What I'm talking about is, for example, a knot.
It's a knot.
If you don't make a knot, you can't make a knot.
What I mean is,
when you make a knot, can you make a knot?
Yes, I'm a knot maker.
But you can't make a knot, right?
Yes.
But I'm asking you,
sometimes you can make a knot,
but you may have to make a knot,
so you don't make sure the knot is penetrating the knot,
otherwise it won't loosen.
But for example,
if you have a knot and the knot is too tight,
it will loosen.
That's what I'm saying,
I'm not talking about penetrating the knot or layers.
Okay, let me ask another question.
Jayden,
your main interest is when the knot is tied,
which can help release the knot.
Is there any function that can be added when working on a string?
Yes.
Actually, we are working on a string with simulation.
We are developing a specialized tool to tie a string.
We are still working on ideas,
but we can develop such functions later.
For example, we can create a string that can be tied to a 3D object.
When we are working on a string, we can create a string that can be tied to a 3D object.
We can create such interfaces.
This is the most important part of the 3D problem.
Yes.
He said that this part of the problem is also a problem for many of our users.
Because it is really difficult to tie a string.
So they are also considering,
but they are still working on an idea.
They are considering a special function to tie a string in the future.
Maybe as long as you set the order of tying a string in this 3D space,
for example, if you set such an order,
it will automatically tie the string for you.
So we are developing such a program.
Okay, thank you.
Do you have any more questions?
Okay.
If that's the case,
we will stop the connection for now.
If you have any questions later,
you can also send them to us at any time.
We will ask them later.
Okay, thank you everyone.
Thank you.